<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EasyCure</string>
    <string name="main_title">We work for and\nfor you 24h daily</string>
    <string name="main_message">Your health will be guarded by us</string>
    <string name="call_us">Call Us</string>
    <string name="health_information">Health Information</string>
    <string name="something_you_want">Something You Want</string>
    <string name="forgot_pwd">Forgot Password ?</string>
    <string name="sign_in">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account yet ? </string>
    <string name="sign_up">  Sign Up</string>
    <string name="sign_up_big">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="health_knowledge">Health Knowledge</string>
    <string name="classify">Classify</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_big">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="contact_big">CONTACT</string>
    <string name="where">Where</string>
    <string name="where_big">WHERE</string>
    <string name="easy_cure">Easy Cure</string>
    <string name="who_we_are">Who We Are ?</string>
    <string name="introduce_us">We are an individual developer and currently studying
        at the Zhuhai College of Beijing Institute of Technology, a student at the
        School of Computer Science. The production of the software was completed by
        2 people and is currently version 1.0.</string>
    <string name="event_name">Event Name</string>
    <string name="event">Event</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="end">End</string>
    <string name="find_article">Find the article</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="schedule_big">SCHEDULE</string>
    <string name="plan">Plan</string>
    <string name="disease_diagnosis">Disease Diagnosis</string>
    <string name="medicine_advice">Medicine Advice</string>
    <string name="eyes_advice">Eyes Advice</string>
    <string name="food_advice">Food Advice</string>
    <string name="sports_advice">Sports Advice</string>
    <string name="sleep_advice">Sleep Advice</string>
    <string name="check_the_body_advice">Check The Body Advice</string>
    <string name="tea_drinking_advice">Tea Drinking Advice</string>
    <string name="main">MAIN</string>
    <string name="prompt">Prompt</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="delete_memo">Are you sure to delete this memo?</string>
    <string name="successfully_deleted">Successfully Deleted</string>
    <string name="successfully_updated">Successfully Updated</string>
    <string name="successfully_added">Successfully Added</string>
    <string name="nothing_to_show">nothing to show</string>
    <string name="find_medicine">Find medicine</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Your Phone Number</string>
    <string name="password">Password Composition:</string>
    <string name="password_pro">Password</string>
    <string name="captcha">Captcha</string>
    <string name="get_captcha">Get Captcha</string>
    <string name="mine">Mine</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="Case">Case Warehouse</string>
    <string name="reset_account">Reset Account</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact">Emergency Contact</string>
    <string name="version_information">Version Information</string>
    <string name="sign_out">SIGN OUT</string>
    <string name="signout_dialog_title">Prompt</string>
    <string name="signout_dialog_message">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="username_can_not_be_empty">Username can not be empty</string>
    <string name="password_can_not_be_empty">Password can not be empty</string>
    <string name="password_length">Password should be between 6 and 13 characters</string>
    <string name="get_code_error">The network speed is slow, please try again later</string>
    <string name="finish_enroll">Finish Registration</string>
    <string name="security_num_not_empty">Security number cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="phone_number_not_empty">Phone number can not be blank</string>
    <string name="finish_setting">Finish Setting</string>
    <string name="Wrong_password_format">Wrong password format</string>
    <string name="setting_successful">Setting Successful</string>
    <string name="wrong_pwd">Wrong Password</string>
    <string name="security_phone_num">Security Phone Num</string>
    <string name="retrieve_password">Retrieve Password</string>
    <string name="find_back_account">You can send a verification code to the previously bound secure phone number to retrieve the account.</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="account_not_empty">Account cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="account_is_empty">Account does not exist</string>
    <string name="account_is_exist">Account is exist</string>
    <string name="check_successful">Successful verification</string>
    <string name="sms_send">SMS has been sent</string>
    <string name="verification_failed">Verification failed</string>
    <string name="reset_account_text">The security number can be successfully modified after passing the verification.</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="some_info_empty">Please complete the information</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="password_inconsistent">Password Inconsistent</string>
    <string name="new_security_phone_num">New security phone num</string>
    <string name="reset_successful">Reset Successful</string>
    <string name="login_num">The number you are logged in to</string>
    <string name="exit">Press again to exit</string>
    <string name="title_no_empty">Title can not be empty</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="check_update">Check Update</string>
    <string name="release_notes">Release Notes</string>
    <string name="version_Information">Version Information</string>
    <string name="service_agreement">Service Agreement</string>
    <string name="automatically_update">Automatically Updates</string>
    <string name="latest_version">Latest Version</string>
    <string name="detected_latest_version">Detected The Latest</string>
    <string name="only_wifi">Only WiFi</string>
    <string name="never">Never</string>
    <string name="automatic_download">Automatic Download</string>
    <string name="version">version</string>
    <string name="version_name">version name</string>
    <string name="release_notes1">EasyCure version 1 is online. Convenient choice of illness, health article related information,
  Good health plan recommendation, excellent hospital and pharmacy location service is the biggest feature of this product, and
    the software supports Chinese and English services.It is convenient for people who can speak Chinese and English.</string>
    <string name="ecure_service_agreement">ECure Service Agreement</string>
    <string name="ec_service_agreement">EasyCure Service Agreement</string>
    <string name="service_agreement1">1.Confirmation of ECure Service Agreement</string>
    <string name="service_agreement2">2.ECure service related definition</string>
    <string name="service_agreement3">3.Service content provided by ECure</string>
    <string name="service_agreement4">4.Registration, use and cancellation of ECure accounts</string>
    <string name="service_agreement5">5.Considerations for using the ECure service</string>
    <string name="service_agreement6">6.Commitment of users legally using ECure services</string>
    <string name="service_agreement7">7.User rights protection and information protection</string>
    <string name="service_agreement8">8.Force majeure, exemption and limitation of liability</string>
    <string name="service_agreement9">9.Protection of intellectual property rights</string>
    <string name="service_agreement_foreword">Thank you for choosing ECure service. The ECure Service Agreement (hereinafter referred to
    as this Agreement) is signed by the ECure Team (hereinafter referred to as us)</string>
    <string name="service_agreement1_content">1、Please read the contents of this agreement carefully. If you have any
        questions about the content of this agreement or the information on the page, please do not proceed to the next
        step. You can consult by adding ECure official QQ: 844964206, so that we can explain and explain for you. By clicking
        on the page or by other means, you agree to this Agreement.\n
    2.If we modify this agreement, we will notify you by popping up the window. If you are unable to agree to change the
        content of the revised agreement, you have the right to stop using the related services; if the two parties agree,
        the relevant services and corresponding agreement contents may be changed separately.\n
    3.If you are a person without civil capacity or a person with limited capacity for civil conduct, please inform your
        guardian and read this agreement and use our services under the direction of your guardian. If you are not a user
        within the territory of the People\'s Republic of China (for the purposes of this agreement, excluding Hong Kong,
        Macao Special Administrative Region and Taiwan), you must also abide by the laws of your country or region, and you
        will confirm that you have entered into and traveled this Agreement. Violation of laws and regulations of the country
        or region in which you belong, reside or conduct business or other business.</string>
    <string name="service_agreement2_content">1、ECure account (or \"account\"): refers to the account that you obtained after you
        obtained the ECure login account and verified by mobile phone for you to use the ECure service.\n
    2、ECure login account: refers to the mobile phone number that receives the verification code during the process of registering
        the ECure account. This mobile phone number will be used as the login account of your ECure account.\n
    3、Identity element: refers to the information element we use to identify you. Currently, we only support SMS verification code
        verification.\n
    4、Nickname: refers to the account name that you open to the public. We treat the user\'s account number (ie mobile phone number)
        confidentially, that is, do not disclose the mobile phone number.\n
    5、Official QQ: 844964206</string>
    <string name="service_agreement3_content">1、Condition selection: The user selects the relevant condition in combination with his or
        her own symptoms, and further confirms the condition according to the clinical manifestation corresponding to the condition.
        After selecting the disease, a medical record will be generated. The user can roughly judge the current physical condition
        according to the description in the case, and the recommended drugs corresponding to the relevant disease are also given in
        the case.\n
    2、Drug recommendation: We recommend several drugs with higher sales and heat for the basic symptoms selected by the user, but only
        for screening. The drugs recommended by the system can only be used as users.The reference drug for selecting a basic condition,
        such as a serious condition, is not a target of the service, and it is strongly recommended that you go to the hospital in time. \n
    3、Health Information: We will update the Health Information Module regularly to ensure that users can learn some of the common
        health tips in the life of the article and keep the user\'s health information fresh in a regularly updated way.\n
    4、Health knowledge: We will make recommendations on the main parts of the body or some living habits, and let the user know
        how to do a good job of health and maintenance, so as to develop a good habit.\n
    5、Memo: The memo function is provided in the software, allowing the user to write the memo content in the software. When the user
        uses the software again, he will pay attention to the memo information recorded before.\n
    6、Positioning: We use the positioning system of Gaode map to provide users with location services
        for surrounding hospitals and pharmacies.\n
    7、Internationalization: The software provides Chinese and English bilingual support services, and automatically selects the
        display language according to the user\'s mobile phone time zone. </string>
    <string name="service_agreement4_content">1、Registration: All services are available after registration is complete. The nickname
        you set in your account will be visible to the outside world, and your mobile number (ie login account) will be kept confidential.\n
        2、Login: We only provide login for this platform (registered users of this platform).\n
        3、Use: The identity element allows us to identify the basis of your identity, please be sure to keep it safe.
        The operation using the identity element and the instructions issued are deemed to be made by you. The account,
        password and other information caused by your reasons are fraudulently used, stolen or illegally used, and the
        risks and losses caused by you are at your own risk.\n
        4、Logout: You can only apply for cancellation of your own account and cancel it in accordance with our procedures.
        In order to protect the legitimate interests of you and other users, the account you apply for cancellation should
        have no unresolved rights or obligations or other disputes arising from the cancellation of the account. There are
        no outstanding transactions.</string>
    <string name="service_agreement5_content">1. Authentication: In the process of identity verification, please keep the network environment unblocked, and ensure that the network environment is safe and you can log in and check the symptoms. \n
     2, the disease query, we launched the disease inquiry service, according to the type of disease - clinical performance to correspond to the user\'s own situation, to determine what type of disease is probably, and provide recommended drugs for reference. But this is only a recommendation and can only be used as a reference. in case
     Users can indeed determine their own symptoms such as: cough and other common symptoms, you can refer to the results of drug recommendations to buy drugs, and if the user is not sure about the specific disease and the condition is more serious, then do not act
     The service object of this function, and it is strongly recommended that the user go to the hospital in time for medical treatment. \n</string>
    <string name="service_agreement6_content">1、You are required to abide by the laws and regulations of the People\'s Republic of China
        and the countries or regions in which you belong, reside or carry out business activities or other business, and may not use our
        services for illegal purposes (including transactions for prohibiting or restricting trading goods). ), nor can we use
        our services illegally.\n
    2、You may not use our services to engage in the infringement of the lawful rights and interests of others or violate national
        laws and regulations, otherwise we have the right to investigate, delay or refuse to settle or stop providing services, and
        you are responsible for any legal liability, such as this leads us or other If the party is damaged, you will be liable for
        compensation.</string>
    <string name="service_agreement7_content">We always adhere to the principle of \"customer first\" and strive to bring you small
        and beautiful changes. We attach great importance to the protection of your information, and strictly implement the information
        security protection system to ensure that your user data will not be leaked, create a good network environment for you, and
        enhance your user experience.</string>
    <string name="service_agreement8_content">Disclaimer\nWe are not liable for the following reasons: We are exempt from
        liability:\n1、Our system is down for maintenance or upgrades;\n
    2、Force majeure causes such as typhoons, earthquakes, floods, lightning or terrorist attacks;\n
    3、Your equipment hardware and communication lines, power supply lines have failed, etc.;\n
    4、Due to your improper operation or use of our services, etc., without our authorization or approval;\n
    5、Due to viruses, Trojans, malicious program attacks, network congestion, system instability, system or device failures,
        communication failures, power failures, banking reasons, third-party services, or government actions.\n
    In spite of the provisions of the preceding paragraph, we will take reasonable actions to actively promote the return of services to normal.\n\n
    Limitation of Liability\n We may provide services to you and your (transactional) counterparty at the same time. You agree
        to expressly waive any actual or potential conflict of interest for such conduct that we may have, and we cannot claim
        that we are providing There is a legal flaw in the service.</string>
    <string name="service_agreement9_content">1、Do not use, modify, decompile, reproduce, publicly transmit, alter, distribute,
        make hairstyles or publicly publish ECure programs or content without our written consent;\n2、Respect for intellectual property
        rights is also your obligation. If there is a violation, you will be liable for damages.</string>
    <string name="security_setting_title">After filling in the security phone number and password to submit, you can complete the account to modify the information</string>
    <string name="fields_not_filled_in">There are fields not filled in</string>
    <string name="problem_help">Problem Help</string>
    <string name="customer_service">My customer service</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="abnormal_function_suggest">Abnormal Function Suggest</string>
    <string name="choose_feedback_type">Choose your feedback type</string>
    <string name="my_customer_service">My Customer Service</string>
    <string name="content_customized">Custom content</string>
    <string name="your_problem">Guess Your Problem</string>
    <string name="commit">Commit</string>
    <string name="feedback_content">（Required）Problem you want to feedback.</string>
    <string name="questions_and_opinions">Questions and opinions</string>
    <string name="abnormal_function_fbi">Abnormal Function：Functional failure or unavailable</string>
    <string name="product_suggestion_fbi">Product suggestion: poor user experience, I have suggestions</string>
    <string name="security_issues_fbi">Security issues: passwords, privacy, fraud, etc.</string>
    <string name="other_problems_fbi">Other problems</string>
    <string name="input_more_than_10_chars">Enter a description of more than 10 words</string>
    <string name="choose_feedback_issue">Choose problems to feedback</string>
    <string name="input_length">Enter at least 10 characters</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="hospital">Hospital</string>
    <string name="drugstore">Drugstore</string>
    <string name="illness_selection">Illness\nSelection</string>
    <string name="illness_selection_title">Illness_Selection</string>
    <string name="positioning">Positioning</string>
    <string name="illness">Illness</string>
    <string name="query_disease">Query Disease</string>
    <string name="history_record">History Record</string>
    <string name="network_anomaly">The network went to Mars.</string>
    <string name="reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="article_lose">The article is missing, we will add it as soon as possible</string>
    <string name="data_getting">Datas are loading，please wait a minute</string>
    <string name="checking_network">Checking The Newwork</string>
    <string name="case_username">Username: </string>
    <string name="illness_name">Illness Name: </string>
    <string name="illness_description">Illness Description: </string>
    <string name="clinical_feature">Clinical Feature: </string>
    <string name="illness_polytype">Polytype: </string>
    <string name="drug_recommend">Drug Recommend: </string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="not_empty">The input cannot be null</string>
    <string name="word_poor">Ah, the word is poor, we will add it as soon as possible</string>
    <string name="phone_num_no_exist">Phone number does not exist</string>
    <string name="phone_num_format_error">Malformed phone number</string>
    <string name="account_not_signup">Account Not Registered</string>
    <string name="code_not_empty">Verification code must be filled</string>
    <string name="wrong_password_format">Wrong password format</string>
    <string name="security_settings_title">Bind the secure phone number. When you need to change the password, the phone number will get a text message and authenticate based on the text message.</string>
    <string name="checking">Checking in progress, please hold on</string>
    <string name="is_remember_pwd">Remember the Password</string>
    <string name="type_select">Type Selection</string>
    <string name="select_tags">Select at least one Tag</string>
    <string name="disease">Disease:</string>
    <string name="polytype">Polytype:</string>
    <string name="symptom">Symptom:</string>
    <string name="reset_account_msg">You can completely reset the secure phone number, username and password bound to your account by completing the following information and verifying it.</string>
    <string name="reLogin">Network abnormal, please login again</string>
    <string name="tag1">Common cold</string>
    <string name="tag2">Headache</string>
    <string name="tag3">Pharyngitis</string>
    <string name="tag4">Mouth ulcer</string>
    <string name="tag5">Acute gastroenteritis</string>
    <string name="tag6">Sprain</string>
    <string name="tag7">Dysmenorrhea</string>
    <string name="tag8">Constipation</string>
    <string name="popular_searches">Popular Searches</string>
    <string name="case1">Case 1 </string>
    <string name="case2">Case 2 </string>
    <string name="case3">Case 3 </string>
    <string name="searching">Searching</string>
    <string name="uploading">Uploading</string>
    <string name="illness_plan">plan</string>
    <string name="security_settings">Security Settings</string>
    <string name="new_username">New Username</string>
    <string name="username_length">Username cannot exceed 10 digits</string>
    <string name="illegal_character">Illegal character</string>
    <string name="modify_username">Change Nickname</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="no_save">Don\'t Save</string>
    <string name="resetCase">has not been processed</string>
    <string name="authentication">Authentication</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="init_data">Initializing Data</string>
</resources>
